askaprepper.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - Ask a Prepper

## Cookies

This website uses cookies (small text files that can be used by websites to make a user’s experience more efficient.

We use cookies to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic, and some of them are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.

We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services.

## Third Party Cookies

### Social Media – Facebook

WE DO NOT SEND (or retrieve) ANY KIND OF PERSONAL INFORMATION TO (or from) FACEBOOK. COOKIES ARE ONLY FOR TECHNICAL PURPOSES LIKE: PLUGIN FUNCTION TO SHARE OR LIKE IF YOU ARE ALREADY LOGGED IN (for more informations on how facebook use cookie please read:

<https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/>

### Analytics – Google Analytics

We use third-party cookies to help us understand how you use our Website and improve your experience.

This information is non-personally identifiable. This information includes IP addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g. HTML pages, graphics, etc.) date/time stamp, and clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

Learn more at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>, and to opt out, visit [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### Performance and Security Cookies – Sucuri

The __cfduid cookie is used to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client basis. It does not correspond to any user ID in your web application, and does not store any personally identifiable information. For example, if the visitor is in a coffee shop where there are a bunch of infected machines, but the specific visitor’s machine is trusted (e.g. because they’ve completed a challenge within your Challenge Passage period), the cookie allows us to identify that client and not challenge them again.

This cookie is strictly necessary for Sucuri’s security features and cannot be turned off.

More info at: <https://sucuri.net/>

### User Experience – Opt In Monster

These cookies are only used to determine if you have subscribed to our mailing list. They determine whether the subscribe pop up will show or not, if you are a subscriber/unsubscriber or not.

## Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will leave our site and go to the site you selected.

Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as us. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services.

Your consent applies to the following domain: www.askaprepper.com

## Data Policy

Personal data will be processed according to the law, in a correct and transparent way. We will collect your data for legitimate purposes. This data is also processed under high security levels. Your data will be retained only until you request removal by contacting our team at support @ askaprepper.com.

You have the right to have access to your data, to be informed, to correct, delete, restrict the use of it.

## Transparency:

  1.     1. Identify Data

Through our systems and our third parties, we might identify data like: e-Mail Address, Name, Social Media Posts, Location, IP Address, Cookies, MetaData.

  1.     1. Manage Data

Through our systems and our third parties, we might manage and classify it in a secure and controlled way. Data can be managed as: active, inactive, subscriber, unsubscriber.

  1.     1. Protecting Data

We protect your data through security check-ups in order to prevent, detect and respond to any possible vulnerability or attack. We prevent attacks through: a physical protection of the database, network security, inventory security, processing security, identity management, access control, encryption and risk mitigation. We monitor and detect the intrusion into the system through by identifying successful attacks, by calculating the impact, by having a disaster recovery plan and by notifying the authorities and the clients.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

  1.     1. Reporting Data

We will use our reporting capabilities in order to document and manage our customer requests.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering/subscribing on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails. The email address may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your interests, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related information, etc.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms and Conditions

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
